http://www.libertybankerslife.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Last updated November 14, 2020.
Because we are sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet, we have adopted the following Privacy Policy for this site. We encourage you to review and become familiar with the following Privacy Policy.
Definitions
“Personal Data” is personal and/or confidential information that relates to you and your account, policy, contract or affiliation with us. “Communications” are any non-confidential and non-proprietary information, except for Personal Data, that you transmit to the site by electronic mail or otherwise, including data, questions, comments and/or suggestions.
“Identifying Information” is any Communication where you knowingly enter your Identifying Information, such as your name, address, social security number, telephone number or e-mail address.
“Non-Personal Information” is any Communication derived from your connection to the site, such as your Internet browser, domain name and referrer link.
All Communications, except for Personal Data and Identifying Information, will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary, will become our property and may be used for any purpose at our sole discretion.
What Information is Collected
In general, you can visit the site while remaining anonymous by not providing any Identifying Information. In some cases, Non-Personal Information may be automatically collected, such as your Internet Browser, computer operating system, domain name of your Internet service provider and/or the website from which you linked to our site. We do not collect your IP address.
Identifying Information about you will not be collected unless you provide it to us voluntarily. For example, we retain e-mail addresses of visitors who respond to the site’s e-mail forms, online forms, registration forms and surveys. we also retain information about the frequency of site visits, length of time of the visit and aggregate information about the site page(s) visitors’ access.
We may send Internet visitors “cookies.” A cookie is a small data file sent by the site to your browser which may then be stored on your hard drive.
Our cookie enables the site to recognize you if you have an account or have utilized certain site features. In addition, the cookie may recall information so that you do not have to re-submit it, and also automatically updates site information. If your browser software permits, you may program it to notify you of attempts to send cookies and/or you may decline or delete them.
When you perform a search with our search engine, we do not record information identifying you or linking you to the search performed. As necessary to provide service, we record limited information for every search request and uses that information only to solve technical problems with the site, to calculate overall usage statistics and to improve the structure and content of the site.
We will primarily use Communications to respond to your request(s). If you choose not to provide a personally identifiable Communication, we may not be able to respond to your request. You may receive an error message displayed on your browser. We may use Identifying Information for feedback purposes, marketing and promotional purposes and for a statistical analysis of users’ behavior. Furthermore, we retain the right to use ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in any Communications you send to the site for any purpose whatsoever, including, but not limited to, developing and marketing products using such information. Non-Personal Information may be aggregated for internal review and used to improve the site’s content and its structure.
We do not distribute Personal Data, Identifying Information or Communications to unaffiliated third parties unless such third parties are under contract with us for administrative support and services or unless required by law.
We will not voluntarily share, rent, sell or otherwise disclose information obtained from visitors to the site, whether Personal Data or Identifying Information, to unaffiliated third parties, unless we have contracted with such third parties to provide administrative support and services or as required by law. In such an event, we will contractually require these service providers to protect such information and provide the same level of confidentiality that we provide.
Information You Choose to Share with LBIG on Our Public Website
We will take appropriate steps to protect all information you share with us. Whenever you provide the site with Personal Data, we will take commercially reasonable steps to establish a secure connection with your web browser.
The site contains secured and non-secured sections. Inherent in the use of the Internet and Internet related technologies is some risk of disclosure of information, including without limitation, personal data you supply. Your use of this site and your entry of information are at your own risk.
We cannot accept responsibility and expressly disclaims all liability for damage or injury that you may incur or that may result from your use of this site or the interception of information you provide, including without limitation, personal data, by a third party.
A Special Note for Parents Concerning Privacy
We encourage children to consult with their parents before furnishing data. However, we believe that parents should supervise their children’s online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a “child friendly” online environment. These tools can also prevent children from disclosing online their name, address, and other Identifying Information without parental permission. For additional information about parental control tools, please consult the “Consumer Assistance” page of the Direct Marketing Association home page at www.the-dma.org.
If We become aware that We have information belonging to someone under the age of legal majority, then We will delete it without request unless We are required to maintain it for legal or regulatory purposes.
California Residents
You have a right to know the information We collect about you and a right to request that We delete it. You may make your request in the same manner that you initially contacted Us and provided your information to Us. For example, you may fill out the “Find the right plan for you” section of Our website to make your request to know or request to delete in the message field. In some instances, we may not be able to honor your request. For example, if We cannot verify you made the request, we cannot verify that the person making the request has the right to act on your behalf, if the request contains incomplete or inaccurate information, or if We are required to retain the information for legal or regulatory purposes.
You may also submit your request to Us in writing at: Liberty Bankers Insurance Group, 1605 LBJ Freeway, Suite 700, Dallas, TX 75234.
Your authorized privacy agent may make a request on your behalf when your privacy agent is able to provide proof that you gave the privacy agent your signed and notarized authorization, or we are able to verify your privacy agent’s authority directly with you.
If you are a current or former client of Ours and also California resident, please call the toll-free number on your policy or contract for additional information about your Right to Know and Right to Delete.
Warranties Disclaimer
Materials on the site are provided “as is” and without warranties of any kind, either express or implied. To the fullest extent permissible under applicable law, we disclaim all warranties, express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose.
We do not warrant that the functions and information contained in the site will be uninterrupted or error-free, that defects will be corrected, or that the server that makes them available is free of viruses or other harmful components. We do not warrant or make any representations regarding the use, or the results of the use, of the materials in web sites maintained by us in terms of their correctness, accuracy or reliability. You, and not us, assume the entire cost of all necessary servicing, repair or correction. Applicable law may not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so the above exclusion may not apply to you. Material on the web sites we maintain is provided solely for general informational purposes.
Any notes, message/billboard postings, ideas, suggestions, concepts or other material submitted will become our property of
and we shall be entitled to use the material for any type of use forever including in any media whether now known or hereafter devised. When you submit material to web sites maintained by us, you agree that we have the right to publish the material for any type of use as outlined above including promotional and advertising purposes.
You agree to indemnify us and our officers, directors, employees, agents, distributors and affiliates from and against any and all third party claims, demands, liabilities, costs, or expenses, including reasonable attorney’s fees, resulting from your breach of any of the foregoing agreements, representations, and warranties.
Email & Postings Received
Do not post any threatening or libelous e-mails or material on this site that would be considered a violation of any law.
We will fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing us to disclose the identity of anyone posting any such e-mails or materials.
Jurisdictional Issues
Unless otherwise specified, the materials in our web sites are presented solely for the purpose of general information. This site is controlled and operated by Liberty Bankers Life Insurance Company from its offices within the state of Texas.
We make no representation that materials in web sites we maintain are appropriate or available for use in other locations. Those who choose to access this site from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable.
This agreement shall be governed by, construed and enforced in accordance with the laws of the state of Texas, as it is applied to agreements entered into and to be performed entirely within such state. Any action you, any third party or we bring to enforce this agreement or, in connection with any matters related to this site, shall be brought only in either the state or federal courts located in Dallas, Texas and you expressly consent to the jurisdiction of said courts. If any provision of this agreement shall be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this agreement and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions. This is the entire agreement between the parties relating to the matters contained herein and shall not be modified except in writing, signed by our authorized officer.
Call us today: 800-731-4300
About Us
Management Team
Company Affiliates
Financial Summary
President's Message
Giving Back
Retirement
1605 Lyndon B. Johnson Freeway, Suite 700 Dallas, Texas 75234
Privacy Policy | Terms of Use
Copyright © Liberty Bankers Life Ins. Co. | All Rights Reserved.
Products not available in all states. For information about your state please call 800-731-4300.
LBL-GWS-CP001
